thehumbledhomemaker.com 2019-06-28

# Privacy Policy | The Humbled Homemaker

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which The Humbled Homemaker, Inc.® collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the [https://www.thehumbledhomemaker.com](https://www.thehumbledhomemaker.com/) website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by The Humbled Homemaker, Inc.®.

 **Personal identification information**

We may collect personally identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, place an order, subscribe to the newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form, purchase a product, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identifiable information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

 **Non-personal identification information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information. This is standard with statistical software like Google Analytics.

 **Web browser cookies**

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. A number of affiliate programs will track the performance of advertising efforts using a cookie, but no personally identifiable information is collected in that process. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert when cookies are being sent. Note that some parts of the Site may not function properly if a computer does not accept cookies.

 **How we use collected information**

The Humbled Homemaker, Inc.® collects and uses Users’ personal information for the following purposes:

  *  _– To personalize user experience_  
We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
  *  _– To improve customer service_  
Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs, especially if you order an eBook or have a question in a comment. The commenting software automatically emails you my answer when I reply. I do not, however, make any lists using the emails I see in comments.
  *  _– To process transactions_  
We may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order to provide service to that order, including ebook updates, and also special offers that may be of interest to you. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.
  *  _– To administer a content, promotion, survey or other Site feature_  
To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them. When you enter a giveaway, we will use the list of emails to send one email announcing the winner or directing entrants to the site to view the winner. It is highly unlikely that we would ever use that list for anything else, but possible.
  *  _– To send periodic emails_  
The email address Users provide for order processing will be used to send them information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, and/or other requests or questions, and will be part of the customer list, which may be used to pass on items of interest to ebook owners. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include daily blog posts, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

 **How we protect your information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

 **Sharing your personal information**

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. (That means I might tell an advertiser how many people clicked on their links or entered their giveaway, but I’ll never share your email addresses or names with them, unless you are the winner of a giveaway.) We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.

 **Payment information**

The Humbled Homemaker, Inc.® does not collect or even see any financial information, including bank account numbers, credit card information, or Paypal passwords. The eBook store send customers directly to Paypal where all monetary transactions take place. We can submit a refund through Paypal and see that you have paid, but that is the extent of our dealings with finances. We are not liable for any compromise of sensitive information that may occur while using external websites like Paypal and others.

 **Third party websites**

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

The Humbled Homemaker, Inc.® participates in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to amazon.com.

 **Advertising**

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. (I don’t think any of my ads actually do that, but they may, or may someday.)

 **Google Adsense**

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at [http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

 **Changes to this privacy policy**

The Humbled Homemaker, Inc.® has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

 **Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

 **Contacting us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:  
The Humbled Homemaker, Inc.®  
https://www.thehumbledhomemaker.com  
Erin Odom, The Humbled Homemaker, Inc.®  
erin@thehumbledhomemaker.com

This document was last updated on December 28, 2017.
